CLARIZA L.

Austin, Texas | cleij893@gmail.com

Compassionate and energetic individual with over 10 years of customer service experience. Soft skills such as verbal and written communication, empathy, prioritization self-management and time management. Dedicated web designer with knowledge in conducting user research, creating user flows, wireframes, and mockups using Figma. I create designs with the user and business in mind. I use HTML, CSS, and JavaScript to breathe life into the design. Visit my portfolio for examples of my work at https://cleija.com.

Experience

Freelance

Design and code client website

- Design client website tailored to the client's requirements and visual standards
- Design both user friendly, and visually appealing user interface
- Develop user flows, wireframes, and mockups for client
- Implement each step of the design process to create well-rounded design
- Create custom graphics for client website via adobe illustrator, adobe photoshop
- Manage and provide ongoing website maintenance for client
- Use of HTML, CSS, and JavaScript to code the design
- Troubleshoot and debug issues that arise in the coding process
- Proficiency in uploading files to servers, and use of hosting platforms
- Manage ongoing website maintenance for client

Community Content Moderator Social Factor - Remote September 2022 to Present

- Represent reputable brands on social media platforms such as Facebook, Twitter, Tik Tok, Instagram.
- Engage with social media communities representing a brand
- Improve security and safety of various social media communities
- Utilize Google suite, Teams, Microsoft Outlook, Asana, and Sprinklr
- Escalate account issues, potential brand risks
- Communicate consistently with Community Managers
- Conduct research on any trending topics or current events

Internet Safety Evaluator

TELUS AI - Remote

December 2021 to Present

- Evaluate social media data based on established company quidelines
- Moderate hundreds of pieces of sensitive social media content per shift
- Investigate the reputation and reliability of content creators, platform users
- Detect and flag web content that is dangerous, deceiving, hateful or harmful
- Mastered and maintained knowledge of company content policies
- Excel in a self-directed environment, managing work duties, schedule making, and time keeping in a remote setting

Captioning Agent

Caption Call/Sorensen Communications - Remote

August 2021 to December 2022

- Facilitate 100+ calls per shift, mastering high call volume
- Caption conversations verbatim using text-to-speech software
- Exceed required company quota and metrics consistently
- Typing over 55+ WPM, proof-reading and editing content with accuracy
- Maintain excellent use of grammar, punctuation, spelling
- Utilize Microsoft teams, Microsoft outlook, and company software daily
- Communicate with team leader, and supervisors to report program bugs, provide feedback, achieve resolutions

Retail Merchandiser

Acosta Sales & Marketing - Austin, TX

May 2021 to November 2021

- Generated 1,000+ dollars in sales per quarter
- Maintained and built business relationships with store management
- Audited hundreds of pieces of data to record sales and marketing information
- Managed inventory, pricing, plan-o-grams and store orders with use of technology
- Ordered product for retailers, merchandised product, built displays
- Trained 2+ employees per quarter
- Created and managed my own schedule to ensure all work is completed
- Completed daily administrative duties such as emails, phone calls, scheduling

Wellness Clerk
Wheatsville Food Co-op
March 2018 to March 2021

- Directed department responsibilities such as inventory management, purchasing product, merchandising, creating signage, supervising customer inquiries
- Increased store sales by educating customers, merchandising displays, creating pricing, auditing and resolving discrepancies
- Accomplished all duties of a receiving clerk such as managing invoices, calculating sub-department billing, communicating discrepancies with store management, quality assurance, requesting credit, processing returns
- Trained and educated new employees, 10+ per year
- Maintained accurate product knowledge of all health, beauty, and grocery items
- Prioritized administrative duties such communication with customers, vendors, management via email, telephone, work social media,
- Purchased and organized customer, special orders, performed customer follow up

Sales Representative
HEB Grocery
March 2017 to January 2018

- Researched and maintained knowledge of the supplement and beauty industry
- Ensured customer retention as an engaging, knowledgeable sales representative
- Secured thousands of dollars in sales for HEB's Healthy Living Department
- Managed duties as a buyer for vitamins, supplements, body care, and housewares
- Purchased department product weekly via store technology, phone, and email
- Coordinated with brand representatives, vendors to organize team training meetings
- Analyzed sales data, used data to place orders and monitor inventory

Cashier and Customer Service
HEB Grocery
October 2014 to March 2017

- Processed hundreds of business transactions per shift
- Inspected and verified tender, checks, state identification
- Resolved customer concerns in an empathetic and professional manner
- Supervised returns, exchanges, complaints
- Trained 3+ new employees per quarter
- Assisted in various crucial roles throughout the company
- Surpassed expectations on yearly company employee reviews

Education

Certification of Web Development
Austin Community College 2021 to 2022
Associate's Degree in Environmental Science and Technology
Austin Community College 2011 to 2014